Hello friends, how
are you all doing on our channel 360 Tamil
Investment? Today we are
going to watch a video on our channel 360 Tamil Investment. Our
subscriber came and asked for a video.
That video is
Star Comprehensive and ICI
Health Shield. We are going to see the difference between these two plans.
Before that, I have a request for you. If
you want medical insurance, call
the number on the screen on WhatsApp and
I will come and get
you a medical copy online. When you
see the age to take the policy, the
maximum age for taking the policy is 65 years.
Children can come and
continue the policy until the age of 25. Similarly, an
individual family
policy can also be taken.
Regarding the ICICI policy, you can take it up to the age of 75.
Similarly,
all children can come and continue the family policy until the age of 20. You
can take an individual family policy.
Next, how many people are covered in the policy?  If
you have heard,
for Comprehensive,
you can get two adults and three children. For ICC, you can get two
adults and two
children. Next,
for insurance, you can get a
policy of up to one crore with Star Health.
Similarly, if
you have seen ICICI Health Shield, you
can get a maximum of 1 crore.
Next, for room rent limit, you can
get any room in ICI. There
is no such limit for two rooms.
For Comprehensive, that is, in the basic plan, they
only give you single AC, but if you take a rider, that is, an
extra product, you will get
all the room facilities.
Before continuing to watch the video, I have a
request for you. If you have not subscribed to this channel yet, then
subscribe. Similarly, when
our videos come to you, press the
bell button next to the notification.
Next, for pre and post
hospitalization, IC will
come and give you 60 days and 90 days of coverage,
similarly, Star Health will also give you the same
coverage.
Next, for the no-fly bonus, you will come and
get a comprehensive 50% for a ₹5 lakh policy, and the next year, another 50% will come. The
total policy that you will get is 7 lakhs or 10 lakhs. If you
take any policy like this, you will get 100% and
the bonus will not increase above that.
Right, for you,
for IC, every
year that you do not have a claim, it will increase by 10% up to a maximum of 100%.
But there is an optional rider here, which
comes with a super no-claim
bonus. If you take that rider,
you will get
50% up to a maximum of 100% for every year that you do not have a claim, as in the Star letter.
Next, for the restore benefit,
IC will come and give you
unlimited  Times will give you but for other
diseases i.e. same person same illness,
coverage is not available. For
you, comprehensive, you will get
100% restoration only once, but for modern
treatment, this restoration will
not work. Next, if you
look at pre-existing diseases, if all the pre-existing diseases are
not pressure, sugar,
cholesterol, any problem like this, you
may have a waiting period for that. In that case, for you, comprehensive, the
waiting period is for three years, but you can reduce
that waiting period by one year by paying extra premium.
For icci health, the
waiting period is only
30 days, which is a very good
advantage. When this
future
comes, they will say that it is 60 days, i.e. specific
surgery, kidney
stone, hernia joint.  Replacement is the same as
cataract, ENT problems,
piles, ulcers, varicose veins, etc.
If you see a waiting period for this, you will get a
two-year waiting period in Star Health Comprehensive,
but for ICI, the waiting period is only
one year.
Next, for maternity treatment, if
you see Star Health, you will get a two-year waiting
period. Similarly, they will
give coverage from 15,000 to one lakh.
Similarly, they will give coverage for a newborn baby
from one lakh to 2 lakh.
For IC, it is optional. If you
say that it is optional, but if you say that it is a rider, it will be
like paying an extra premium.
This comes with a one-year waiting period of
50,000 to one lakh rupees.  The
coverage is the same for a
newborn baby up to 90 days. They will
come and give you
coverage for obesity,
bariatric surgery, and a maximum of 5
lakhs
can be claimed. You can come to ICI and get no
coverage.
Next, if you see that there is any limit for dark spot treatment,
both plans come and there
is no limit.
Next, for health checkup,
you can come to ICI and get a
maximum of ₹5000.
You can
come to ICI and get a specific test and claim.
Next, for ambulance facilities,
both plans come and there
are no conditions. You
can claim any actual amount. Next, for Aagai Ambulance, you can
come to ICI and get a coffee,
but for comprehensiveness, the
maximum is ₹5.  You can claim up to one lakh rupees.
Next, if a person who has taken an RT Road Traffic
Accident policy comes and has an
accident, that is, an accident while driving on the road, then they will come and give you extra coverage.
That benefit comes and
comes in the comprehensive policy and comes with 25% extra coverage.
This benefit does
not come in ICI.
Next, for Ayush treatment, Siddha Unani
Ayurveda and related treatments, if
you come to ICI and
see it, you can claim up to the sum insured,
but for Star Health
Comprehensive, you
can only claim a maximum of 30,000. Next, for out-of-pocket coverage, you can
come to ICI and pay extra
money and get this facility through the rider. Even if
you have a comprehensive policy as default, you can
claim up to a maximum of ₹5,000,
doctor.  You can only claim for a piece of furniture.
Similarly, if you have
no teeth, you can come to them once in three years and claim for eye-
related outpatients. Next, there
is no limit for chemotherapy, robotic surgery, and other modern treatments in ICI. You have a limit for comprehensive
insurance.
Next, let's see the additional benefits. Is comprehensive
insurance free? Accident insurance comes to you. That
is, in case of death or physical
disability, you can come and collect the amount.
Next, you can
claim up to a maximum of ₹2,500 for each day you are hospitalized and receive treatment. As for
ICC, you will be
given coverage for treatment from home. Next, I will come and give coverage for medical items, such as gloves,
masks, sanitizers, and other items.
Comprehensive insurance comes to you and covers more than ₹10 lakh.
This coverage is only given if you take it and
put all the riders. Next, there is the additional summer suit
protector, i.e., you get a bonus. If
you claim it for less than ₹50,000, that bonus will not
come and this ride protector will come as if it has no effect.
Next, there is the sum insured
protector, i.e., inflation, i.e.,
your insurance amount will keep
increasing as money swells. Next, there is the
compensatory cover by paying an additional premium. If the
policyholder goes abroad and
takes some treatment,
does someone from home have to travel and go to that hospital? You can get the coverage for that.
Next, let's see the premium.
We have made a comparison for ₹25 lakh. Even for
comprehensive, if you
write a policy for ₹25 lakh, you will get almost
₹37,000. This is IC.  If you take it,
you will get only ₹14000. So
Star Health has a higher premium.
So
even if you take it, the maximum you will get is
₹30000. But
ICC has half the premium. So no matter
how you look at it, the premium is
very cheap.
Now, what do you think is the best?
I
can't tell you. You can
come and take it, whichever you feel is the best.
Because both plans have
good things and bad
things. So, you can come and take it. You
can see the
important advantage in Star Comprohaven. If
you have seen the important advantage in Star Comprohaven, this is the retail policy. You
get full insurance, that is, a lifetime
renewable guarantee. They give it to you.
Why is this so important? If
you have asked, "What is this?", we are now well and we can take it
whenever we want.  You can come and take it from Star Health,
or HDFC, you
can take a policy from any company,
right? But after a problem arises, no company will come and
give you the policy so easily. Even if they
give it as it is, there will be a lot of waiting periods.
Otherwise, they will give it as
exclusions. Otherwise, they will
put loading. So many problems. Then, when
we are well, we
take a policy from a company that can give life-long renewal. It is very
important that if you take this comprehensive, you get a
second one. If you don't like the
Star
Comprehensive policy,
you can easily port it to another policy from Star Health. Similarly,
you can also change to another company
because this is a retail
policy, and the conditions are the same here. They
won't change everything immediately
because if they change any of the terms
and conditions here,
They can only change it after getting IRT approval.
They won't change everything overnight. Next,
you can come and get this policy through a good agent.
So,
you will get good service.
This is what you get at the bank.
If the bank doesn't come every day,
you will get the
policy at the bank. Then, if you
come to that bank and get the franchise manager or
you are an executive,
who will you contact? Similarly, if the bank comes and goes to another franchise, who will you contact?
Similarly, the bank doesn't come and simply
tells us that it's not 24 hours.
Our only job is to sell the policy. If
you make a claim, you should come and
contact that company directly. So,
how much support will they provide when you make a claim?
We
can't say that we will do it. Next, if
you come to ICI and see an important
advantage, the premium
is very, very low. Maybe
you can't pay the premium for Normal Star Health. In that case,
you can take a low premium policy by saying that you will get coverage for as long as the athlete gets it. Next,
another important
thing I said before is that if you get an
illness, it is not that easy to get a policy. So, if
you have some critical
problem and you
can't get a policy from somewhere else, then you can come and
take this policy. The
underwriting rules are a little simple. So, there is a chance that you will get the policy easily. Similarly, if you see the waiting period, even if
you have some health
problem when you come and take the policy, the waiting period is
very low.  Come and
get coverage. Those who have a
problem can
definitely come and take it from ICI. I
am very healthy. I want a long life. Don't feel like
that.
Come and take it from Star Health. That's all.
Whatever you
think is best, come and think about it. If
you have any ideas or suggestions, please
come and tell me in the comments. If you liked this video,
like, share, subscribe.
To take the same,
call the number on the screen.
Thank you. Hello.